## Travis Trimboli

+1-240-676-1232 | travis.trimboli@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/travistrimboli/ |

#### Summary

Strategic and customer focused engineer with 8+ years working for software development and SaaS organizations in both pre and post-sales. Experience delivering creative solutions to better manage stakeholder relationships and increase product value. Responsible for facilitating strong collaboration between the customer and cross-functional teams

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, SQL, GraphQL, YAML, Bash, JavaScript

Development Tools: Atlassian (JIRA, Bitbucket, Confluence), Git, Ansible, Terraform, Postman, Kubernetes, Docker

Management: Salesforce, Gainsight, ChurnZero, Pendo, Aha! Cloud Platforms: AWS, Azure, Google Cloud Platform

#### EXPERIENCE

## • ThreatQuotient

Customer Success Engineer

Reston, VA / Remote

Feb 2019 - Present

- Guided the development of the Customer Success program from the outset with tasks including:
  - \* Advised in defining the Customer Success Engineer role and responsibilities.
  - \* Helped define the operational, tactical, and strategic approaches applied by the team.
  - \* Introduced customer success metrics and KPIs and ways to track them.
  - \* Adapted new tools and technologies to streamline processes and improve efficiency.
- Managed all of North America, including commercial, federal, and DoD customers ranging from enterprise level organizations Fortune 100 and 500 to SMBs.
- Served new and existing clients and partners as trusted advisor to drive outcomes and deliver value.
- Actively collaborated with internal teams, such as product management and engineering, to communicate customer feedback, helping contribute to continuous improvement initiatives.
- Prioritized gathering customer feedback and requirements to align product roadmap priorities with customer needs better.
- Championed the creation of a new service offering to better enable customer efficiency (under review).
- Provided client services centered around deployment, training, integration support, and troubleshooting.
- Contributed to the development of front-end and back-end components of the platform, as well as custom integrations.
- Provided testing and QA support for platform features, integrations, and other applications.

# • Carbon Black Threat Analyst

Boulder, CO

Aug 2018 - Feb 2019

- Participated in a 24/7 SOC team working on rotating schedules.
- Performed endpoint security monitoring, security event triage, and incident response for a mid-size organization.
- Collaborated with other team members and management to document and report incidents to customers.
- Maintaind records of investigated security events and incident response activities utilizing case management and ticketing systems.
- Take on Security Operations responsibilities when not on a SOC shifts including: documentation, basic malware analysis, exceptions tracking, security tool management, tuning, and configuration, along with metrics and reporting.
- Contributed to the development of front-end applications to support SOC team operations.

Waltham, MA

Sales Engineer

- Oct 2017 Aug 2018
- $\circ\,$  Configured and presented product demonstrations for prospects, customers, and partners.
- Served as a client-facing technical resource supporting the sales organization.
- Completed product RFI/RFP's for all three products as they present themselves.

- Coordinated product evaluations and proof of concepts for prospects.
- Assisted product management with documenting usuability and feature feedback.
- Supported prospect and customer implementations and continued success using the products.
- Provided internal support for any troubleshooting related inquiries.
- Examined potential threats providing analysis on how each product would respond.

## • Fidelis Cybersecurity

Bethesda, MD

Account Manager

Feb 2016 - Oct 2017

- Conducted outbound and inbound B2B prospecting by phone and email of potential Commercial and Federal customers, and Channel partners.
- Communicated core value propositions of Fidelis products and services to C-suite individuals of all industries.
- Qualified prospect needs, timelines, and budgets for the outside account team to accelerate the right prospects through the sales cycle.
- Attended trade shows and partner functions to represent Fidelis, showcasing product components and gathering user feedback.

## **EDUCATION**

## • University of Maryland Global Campus

Master of Science in Information Technology; GPA: 4.00

Adelphi, MD

Aug 2017 - May 2020

## • University of Maryland

Bachelor of Arts; GPA: 3.80

College Park, MD

Aug 2008 – May 2013

#### CERTIFICATIONS

- AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner
- CompTIA Securit+

#### **PROJECTS**

- QuantSoftware Toolkit: Open source Python library for financial data analysis and machine learning for finance.
- GitHub Visualization: Data visualization of Git log data using D3 to analyze project trends over time.
- Recommendation System: Music and movie recommender systems using collaborative filtering on public datasets.
- Mac Setup: Book that gives step-by-step instructions on setting up developer environment on macOS.